That must be them there near
that big piece of nothing.
According to my GPS.
it's where Texas turns into Oklahoma.
Oh. great.
right in the middle
of a jurisdictional pissing contest.
Look. I'm out of water.
Give me yours.
Are y'all FBI?
FBI Special Agent Seely Booth.
This here is Dr. Temperance Brennan
from the Jeffersonian.
- Welcome to Oklahoma. ma'am.
- Welcome to Texas. ma'am.
Guy. welcome
to the United States of America.
- Where are the remains. please?
- Oh. right here.
Hardly any flesh left.
It's very dry here.
so I'm guessing the time of death
was some months ago.
How do you think they died?
They left Oklahoma. hit Texas.
then died of despair.
Nope. they're definitely Oklahomans.
If they were from Texas.
they'd had sense to carry water.
That wouldn't show up in the bones.
No clothing.
Might have blown away.
Maybe a young couple.
some kind of suicide pact?
Sub-pubic angle
suggests two females.
- Lesbian suicide pact.
- Definitely Texans. then.
The victims were Pygopagus.
or some would say Illeopagus.
- What?
- Greek?
- Conjoined twins.
- What's that?
Siamese twins.
The point of attachment
is posterior.
Joined at the ass.
Definitely Texans.
- So what do we got here. Doc?
- It's a federal case. boys.
The FBI will take jurisdiction.
Conjoined twin births
occur once every 85.000 births.
The same frequency
as hermaphroditic births.
Oh. Mr. Nigel Murray.
we've so missed your insights.
- Thank you.
- Why weren't the remains
dispersed by scavengers?
The depression
in the earth suggested that
that they were buried
in an extremely shallow grave.
The remains were spotted by
an oil survey team from a helicopter.
The question is.
what exposed the bones?
Well. there was a sandstorm
in that area eight days ago.
Sustained winds of 60 miles an hour.
gusts of about 80.
Their molars have not completely emerged
and root development is incomplete.
Indicating that the victims were
between 19 and 21 years of age.
Guys. hello?
ID'ing them is not going
to be a problem.
How many sets of conjoined twins
can there be?
Over the last 500 years.
approximately 600 sets.
Over 70% women.
I did not expect him to know that.
Well. all facts are useful.
It's just the context that shifts.
I bet I could just go search for
missing Siamese twins
and find them in. like. ten minutes.
By all means. give it a shot.
The victims had two
separate spinal columns
fused distally at the lower
sacral level extending to the pelvis.
No other vertebral anomalies.
Neither one of them could've survived
the death of the other.
So murder-suicide.
Suicide-murder.
- Or vice-versa.
- That was vice-versa.
Soil beneath the skeletons
was full of weirdness.
Quite a bit of decomposed cotton.
We didn't see any fabric.
Wow. it's decomposed.
It's fairly cheap stuff. too.
I think they were wrapped in a sheet.
Naked. wrapped in a sheet.
Sweets will've something to say
about that.
Also I found soil-dwelling mites:
Genus Ameronothrus.
Nearest place they could've picked up
soil mites was hundreds of miles away.
And decomposed popcorn.
- They were killed at the movies?
- I have a theory...
The circus.
Kind of stole my thunder there.
But. yeah. yeah.
the traveling circus.
I found them.
Already?
- The circus.
The circus.
"Abracadabra" was first uttered
to cure hay fever.
Conjoined twins wrapped in a sheet?
According to Hodgins.
It would help to know
how they were wrapped.
All the evidence is gone with wind.
- No other clothing?
- According to Hodgins.
The murder didn't want anyone
to identify them from their clothes.
They're conjoined twins.
You might as well buried them with
their driver's licenses in their hands.
Wrapped naked bodies
often indicate a careful burial.
or of course. sexual assault.
You know what?
That's creepy.
We got to get going there.
- Where?
- Texas. That's where the circus is.
Circus folk are extremely
tight-lipped and close-knit.
- They won't tell you anything.
- How do you know?
I... you know. I've read articles.
You're the worst liar I have ever met.
You read articles?
Even I know he's lying.
Okay. I'm adopted.
You know what?
My story isn't important here.
No. it's very important.
Go ahead.
I...
when I reached the age of majority.
I tried to find my birth mother.
a psychic who worked the circus
and carnival circuit in Florida.
Bio mom was a carney.
You know what?
Let's stay on track.
The point is
no one would talk to me.
- Were you wearing a suit?
- You'll be wearing a suit.
they won't open up to you. either.
I'm just trying to be helpful here.
I suspect Sweets is right.
I studied a carnival
for six weeks as research
for my cultural
anthropology dissertation.
no one would tell me anything.
Even though I became
quite adept on the high wire.
Fine. If they're going to talk
to their own. we will go undercover.
- What?
- If we're joining a circus.
we'll need an act.
I am quite adept on the high wire.
No. we'll have a knife-throwing act.
- I can't throw knives.
- I can.
I had the best knife skills
in the Rangers.
We're going to join the circus.
Bones - Season 04 Episode 12
"Double Trouble in the Panhandle"
Synchro: ShalimarFox. IceFreak
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--
OK. so we're going to talk
to the twins'mother here in Ft. Worth.
then we'll pick up our mobile home.
And we'll join the circus
right outside Waco.
- "Our mobile home"?
- Yeah. we're circus folks. Bones.
We crisscross the country
in a mobile home.
I'll have the field office here
paint up something special for us.
Is that all you need to get a job
at the circus. a mobile home?
You know what? It's going to help.
It's showy.
we're show people.
It's always possible that
we'll talk to the girls'mother
and solve this whole case tonight.
- Right?
- I hope not.
What?
I should've never let those girls
leave this home.
Worst thing that can happen
to a mother. isn't it?
Finding out
that you outlived your child.
- Unnatural.
- Except for societies with
infant mortality rates.
My understanding is you tried to sue
the circus several times. Mrs. Van Owen.
It's Mrs. Hicks.
Dell Hicks here
is my husband and my lawyer.
- Dell helped me sue the circus for...
- Loss of income.
alienation of affection.
civil rights abuses.
animal abuses. improper hiring.
emotional distress.
mental anguish...
- Any of these go to court?
- It's just a matter of time.
- You really hated that circus.
- They stole my daughters.
I'll do anything
to get back at them for that.
- When did you last see your daughters?
- Four months ago.
They told us
to butt out of their lives.
Jenny did.
If one of the girls
wanted something.
it was the same
as both of them wanting it.
If Jenny wanted something.
then they both want wanted it.
Didn't matter what Julie wanted.
I took a look at their remains. and
I had to wonder if you ever considered
having them surgically separated?
It was too dangerous.
I disagree.
So did Jenny and Dr. Muir.
Well. Julie and I thought
it was too dangerous.
Your daughters disagreed on whether
or not they should be separated?
Dr. Muir's office here
in Fort Worth?
I'm sure you understand
that my responses
to your questions about
the Van Owen sisters is
is somewhat tempered
by patient privilege.
Well. they're murder victims. right?
Patient privilege no longer applies.
Ah. yes. of course.
I've never had
a patient murdered before.
You thought that the twins
could safely be separated.
- Yes.
- I agree.
As did Jenny.
But Julie and her mother disagreed.
She and her...
ambulance chaser husband
tried to sue me.
- So how did you leave things?
- Well. in the end.
it didn't matter what
the rest of us thought.
Julie and Jenny were going
to have to come to an agreement.
I wonder if they thought
they could continue
to work in the circus
if they were separated?
Well. they both loved the circus.
Jenny told me once that they had
some ideas on
how to expand their act.
Sounds like Jenny was the bossy one
and Julie was a little nicer?
They were like any other sisters.
They had distinct personalities
and strengths.
If there's anything else
I can do to help the FBI...
Yeah. tell you what. Why don't you send.
the records to the FBI in Washington.
- Why can't you simply take them?
- We have another appointment.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The FBI did a wonderful job
with this trailer.
Okay. just lose
the Katharine Hepburn voice.
I'm just trying to find my character.
you know. acting.
Well. don't.
It sounds ridiculous. okay. Bones?
What's my name there. Wanda?
It's written right there on the side
of the truck. which "high wire" is not.
It's just sometimes you get irritated
and you say "Booth" without thinking.
I don't do anything without thinking.
ever... Buck.
Buck and Wanda
and their Knives of Death?
- Never heard of you.
- We worked the Pacific Northwest.
Canada. Alaska.
I guess that makes you
the beautiful assistant then?
Wanda. yes. I'm also
quite adept on the high wire.
I got to admit. it would be nice to have
a knife-throwing act around.
Well. folks.
they love a little danger.
- So what's your thing?
- Our thing?
Yeah. your gimmick.
You know.
cowboy and Indian princess?
Pirate and kidnapped princess?
Jack the Ripper and princess?
- We're Russian.
- Or Cowboy and Indian princess thing.
No. no.
the Russian thing sounds good.
- It does?
- Yeah.
OK. yeah. We're Russki.
All right. Well. you do
the first show for free.
and if I like you.
then we talk payment.
You... you ain't seen nothing yet.
You two
ain't the first of May. are you?
- No. In fact. we are not...
- We are no first of May.
We're no first of May.
This is Lavalle.
He's our 24-hour man.
Lavalle. meet Buck and Wanda Moosejaw.
They do a barber act.
Moosejaw?
- What are you. Indian?
- Canadian.
He will show you
where to park your digs.
- You can get ready for the show.
- They any good?
How about that?
Being able to splinter a post
don't make you any kind of a showman.
Oh. we're show people. all right.
You will be amazed.
- Russian? You had to pick Russian.
- I know. Brilliant. right?
- It just popped into my head.
- You know what?
Don't pop things. Bones.
Sweets. what the hell
is the first of May?
A newbie. A rookie.
Why would a little person
be referred to as a 24-hour man?
Oh. having a little trouble
with the lingo?
He is the advance person.
He goes to town ahead of the circus
and sets everything up. If you like.
I could e-mail you a lexicon.
I would certainly appreciate that.
Sure.
Can I offer a piece of advice?
That's why we called you. Sweets.
Don't try too hard
to be their friends.
Act like you're more interested
in each other than any of them.
All right? They will come to you.
Okay. thanks.
So... sex. right?
Oh. good idea.
Okay.
Okay. well. I think
what we need to do is
get a syncopated rhythm
going that takes advantage
of the natural frequency
of the springs.
Are you this spontaneous
during real sex?
Yes. I am.
What do you think?
Let's just hope they're as good
outside the trailer as they are in.
I'll give them good marks
for staying power.
- I don't know what that is.
- I can try to balance.
- Getting settled in. Moosejaw?
- Yep.
Nice tent. Very...
- It's a piece of crap.
- Right.
Let's just pray
there's no wind or rain.
Hate for it to collapse
on paying customers.
- There something we can help you with?
- Aim me at the Van Owen sisters.
- The Van Owen sisters?
- Yeah. sisters. jugglers.
Julie and Jenny. joined at the hip.
Literally.
Yeah. funny.
How do you know them?
I worked a carney up
in Alaska last year.
Nice kids. Said they were
coming down here to work at Bingham's.
I'm afraid you missed them.
They... they moved on...
Well. when was it. Lavalle?
After Petersburg. wasn't it?
Julie and Jenny
don't work here anymore.
- Where'd they go?
- You know what?
I think I got a note in here
somewhere from them that they left.
"Thanks for everything. We loved
working here. and we love all of you.
"but we've decided to take
another direction in our lives.
"You'll always be family.
Love. Julie and Jenny."
- Doesn't sound like them.
- It sounds like Julie.
- Not Jenny.
- Well. maybe
they were forced to leave
under duress.
Listen to the five-dollar words
the target can use.
She likes to read the dictionary.
Tough girl. Jenny.
Yeah. the rubes sure loved them.
Them quitting probably hurt
your box office.
Sweetheart...
I got nothing but trouble
at the box office.
I'm sure we'll run into the girls
somewhere or another. I mean.
there's not many circuses
anymore. right?
Food's ready in the mess tent.
If you two can drag yourselves
out of your trailer. I'll
introduce you
to the rest of the gang.
"Duress"?
- Real smart.
- What? Why?
- Just because I'm in a carnival.
- Forget it.
Doesn't mean I can't read books
and have a good vocabular...
Is it more impressive that they can
do that joined at the hip or less?
Twins die an average
of ten years apart.
even when they are
genetically identical.
Not helpful.
Ah. X-rays from
the twins'doctor in Dallas.
Okay. notice the antemortem
bone lesion in the carpal capitate.
suggesting a stab wound on the hand.
Did you see the video?
They were juggling machetes.
Found particulates of magnesium
carbonate on both girls.
Do you have any
fascinating trivia on that subject?
One man's trivia
is another man's wisdom.
The chalk used in flooring.
fireproofing. cosmetics.
toothpaste and laxatives.
Obviously. we are on
the lookout for a clean-toothed.
eye shadow wearing.
constipated contractor.
Brennan sent a photograph of the note
the twins left at the circus.
How long will it take you
to analyze it?
I found something pretty interesting
just by looking at it.
You said Jenny
was the left-handed twin.
- Yes.
- Correct.
The smudges and the slants
on the letter indicate
that the note was written
by the left-handed twin.
On a standard keyboard.
there are over 3.000 words that can be
touch-typed with the left hand alone.
It's not typed; it's handwritten.
How many can be typed
with the right hand?
450. Thank you ever
so much for asking me.
Please don't encourage him.
The point is. "Jenny"
was signed with a right hand.
while "Julie"
signed the note with a left.
This note was obviously
not written by them. guys.
It's fake.
Can you look at them?
Clowns.
The psychiatric term for
fear of clowns is coulrophobia.
It's not fear; it's hate. okay?
Big difference.
- You mind?
- Sure. have a seat.
Buck. Wanda. this is
Magnum the Strongman.
and this is Madame Nina.
- Oh. are those your legal names?
- Is Wanda yours?
Buck and Wanda...
they knew Jenny and Julie.
I miss those girls.
We all do.
- Not the clowns.
- Why is that?
The girls were trying a new act.
They borrowed some of the clowns'
equipment without asking.
- They should have stuck to juggling.
- They were trying to save the circus.
They wanted more time
in front of the audience.
Not Julie. she wanted
to spend more time with her boyfriend.
- Julie had a boyfriend?
- But her sister was
literally right beside her
all the time.
People can't help
who they fall in love with.
When you fall in love with an outsider.
that's the end of circus life.
- Who was it?
- He was a gillie.
- What's a gillie?
- A gillie's an outsider.
So. one of the girls had a boyfriend.
You're sitting on my clothes.
Sorry.
but it's kind of tight in here.
Which is why you shouldn't throw
your underwear on the floor.
- They fell.
- No.
don't blame gravity
for a lack of tidiness.
Is there only one bed there?
Can we please hit rewind?
One of the girls had a boyfriend?
- Yes.
- Only one of them?
I mean. how did they.
you know. when they were...
- I don't see physically how they...
- Okay. look. that's not the issue.
Just take that image
out of your mind and pretend
that they are separate individuals.
and ask yourself if you found anything
that suggested a relationship.
Yeah. sorry. Still working on
the mind picture eradication thing.
Did you find anything
on one of the sisters
that you didn't find
present on the other?
Yeah. actually. Yeah. I did.
Residue of polyelectrolyte polymers
under the fingernails of Julie.
and not Jenny.
It was polyvinylpyrrolidone.
What is that. makeup?
It's not makeup; it's hair gel.
Seems that Julie was running
her fingers through someone's hair.
- Julie was the one with a boyfriend?
- Can you identify a brand?
No. but it would smell
a lot like sandalwood.
Smooth sure Power Hold.
It's definitely on the list
of possible products. yeah.
Dr. Muir was wearing a ton of hair gel
that smelled just like sandalwood.
What? Son of a barber. OK?
I know my traditional hair products.
So. Julie was having an affair
with Dr. Muir?
If we leave now. we can question them
and be back in a couple of hours.
No. not in this thing.
And we have a show.
We can't be late.
We're not circus performers. okay?
We solve murders.
Yeah. we're undercover
murder solvers.
and if we don't make it back in time.
we'll blow our cover.
Tell you what. I will search
for a faster vehicle. All right?
Oh. but first.
I got to go scavenge. you know.
some Russian costumes because
somebody said we did a Russian act.
It was a great idea.
Dr. Brennan.
if you do have to perform.
any chance that you could
set up a Webcam so we could watch?
You know. to see if we might be
of any help with the case. I mean.
Yeah. absolutely. Anything to help.
- You bring our real clothes?
- Yes. they're in the bag.
Where did you learn
to drive this thing?
You're kidding me. right?
I'm a cop.
We should really talk about our act.
Two complementary fractures
on each of the victims'craniums.
Like their heads were
cracked together?
- Interesting fact.
- Yes. but is it pertinent?
Indeed.
In the fraternity of forensic
anthropologists.
these are known as
"kissing fractures."
Heads knocked together
is the cause of death?
Little known fact.
There were actually six men
known as the three stooges.
So. we're going with the three
stooges as the cause of death.
Such would be my inclination.
I'll let you pass that nugget
on to Dr. Brennan
when you tell her
about the fractures.
I already sent off
the girls'medical records.
I'm not sure how else
I could help you.
I want to run my fingers
through your hair.
- Why?
- To prove you were
in a sexual relationship
with Julie VanOwen.
And running your fingers
through my hair will prove that?
I tell you what. look Dr. Brennan up
on the an internet.
She's getting very famous
for this kind of stuff.
You're not gonna understand this.
- You had a threesome?
- Absolutely not.
I dated Jenny first.
and then I fell in love with Julie.
Jenny didn't really like that.
That's why he recommended
separating the twins.
That's not true.
My recommendation was
totally objective.
Maybe their mother found out
and sued his life away.
Which is the only reason we kept
the relationship a secret.
Relationship.
- Sexual relationship?
- How?
Well. when you were...
I'm trying to understand.
- When you and Julie...
- The girls had separate genitalia.
A fair amount of privacy
could be achieved
by an eye mask and an mp3 player
turned up very loud.
Julie liked the kings of leon.
Jenny liked maroon 5.
The american medical association is
going to take away your license.
- That's a motive for murder.
- We should arrest him.
Wait. On what charges?
Definitely positive for the whole
suspicion of murder thing. but.
you know. the other thing is just.
it's a little confusing.
Can you go faster?
We'll miss the show.
We're making great time. bones.
All right. relax.
All right. a little help there.
Phone's ringing. I'm kind of busy.
Okay.
Should we talk about our act?
We need costumes.
We don't need the russian costumes.
We're dropping the act.
What?
You can throw knives. I saw it.
I know I can. but we caught
the bad guy. all right.
We don't need to go undercover.
What are you doing?
Digging for loose change?
Got it.
Special agent seeley booth's phone. dr.
Temperance brennan speaking.
Dallas field office.
It's for you.
Yeah. of course it is.
It's my phone.
Then ask'em what they want.
What is this about. please?
They say that all of Dr. Muir's
alibis checked out and they can't
hold him for murder.
He didn't kill the twins?
He couldn't have driven
all the way to
the texas/oklahoma border
during that time.
Now can we talk about our act?
- I do know a few words in russian.
- Oh. no.
Vincent provided me with
the approximate forces
it would take to cause the kissing
fractures to the twins'skulls.
Approximately 300 pounds
per square inch.
which is. by the way.
the same as a pit bull's bite.
- Were they attacked by a pit bull?
- Not a likely scenario.
See how this works. mr.
Nigel-murray?
A kind of mental winnowing process?
Okay.
Scenario number one.
Whiplash.
No.
No?
There'd be evidence of trauma
in the vertebrae as well.
Excellent mental winnowing.
Okay. Scenario number two.
A fall.
The rest of the skeleton would
have showed evidence of a fall.
Scenario number three.
they are assaulted separately
by a weapon.
That's possible.
- No. actually it's not.
- Why not?
Because the wounds are
absolutely symmetrical here.
The possibility of an assailant
striking them separately
at the exact same angle
with the exact same force...
It ain't going to happen.
Okay. well. the heads could
have been conked together.
There'd be evidence on
the soft tissue of the face.
There was no soft tissue left.
What if the blunt
instrument was soft?
Like a pillow?
Oh. wait a second.
Clown props.
- I'll call booth and Dr. Brennan.
- Nice.
When cortez conquered the aztecs.
clowns were among the many treasures
he carried back to clement VII.
Thank you.
- You ready?
- Yes.
Ready to throw knives
at beautiful woman.
- Not at. I hope.
- Right. no. of course.
Around her.
Wow. wanda.
You look...
You too. boris.
You make beautiful natasha.
Man. you. you act like it's
the first time you've done this.
We like to keep things fresh.
So I've seen.
Okay. so...
I stand against a board.
right. with balloons all
around me and then
you pop them
with your razor sharp knives?
Right. Unless we do our actual
job and find the murder weapon.
What's with the moustache?
- I thought it'd add a russian flair.
- It looks like a small animal.
There's a giant
plastic ice cream cone.
giant plastic shoe.
giant plastic phone.
giant plastic...
- You mind telling me what you're doing?
- Or what. you're going to play tough?
You're clowns. right?
I throw knives.
- Let's kick his ass.
- Bring it on. bozo.
Uh. we're just looking
for a prop that's all.
Buck here is going to knock
this nose off my face with a knife.
Why does everyone think the clown
stuff is there for everyone?
This is our stuff!
Let's kick his ass. you guys!
Traditionally.
clowns are fun loving and anarchistic.
You are rigid and humorless.
Let's kick both their asses!
You better have your biggest
ass-kicking shoes on.
Stop!
Y'all want to have a clem. that's
your business. but after the show.
Tumbles. I'm serious.
All right. let's go. guys.
Not so funny now. hey. tumbles?
That's enough. moosejaw.
We're lining up.
You two damn well better be ready.
I'm ready.
How about you?
- Oh. god! Bones
- My eye.
You okay?
I'm okay.
Well. we can't do the show now.
What? No!
The show must go on!
Says who?
Ladies and Gentlemens.
and children of all ages.
Welcome to bingham's
circus of wonders.
The most sensational. death-defying
one ring spectacular
on Earth.
They're clapping for us.
Smile. Boris. And wave.
Show them your knives!
Come on.
Where's the buck moosejaw I married?
- I got props.
- Props? For what?
Props. Objects for you
to throw knives at.
No. no. You are going to
stand against the board still.
I am going to throw knives around you.
But not too close.
That does not sound
like a very good act.
I'm sure the crowd is
expecting a lot more than that.
There is no act. Remember?
There's just me trying
not to kill you.
What... you said you were very good.
trained in knife skills by the military.
I am very good.
But it's you I am concerned for.
Well. if you say you're skilled then
I have no reason to doubt you. do i?
You know it's not good for
the barbers to fight before a show.
Those things are sharp.
Let's just get through this.
all right. mrs. Moosejaw?
Okay.
Look at that.
The clowns are using
those fake barbells.
One of them could've clocked
the twins
and smashed their heads together.
The bar joing the foam
weights together is too short.
The fulcrum wouldn't give
any of them sufficient force
to cause the kissing fractures.
But they're clowns.
They have their ways.
You're up.
And now.
direct from their triumphant
tour of europe and the far east.
bingham's circus of wonders
is proud to present
the razor sharp skills
of the most thrilling.
the most breathtaking.
the most dangerous
knife throwing act in the world.
Boris and natasha...
and their russian knives of death!
What's up with brennan's eye?
An eye patch.
That's very rakish.
Plus she only has to
be half as scared.
Bones. just keep your arms
outstretched like...
This. Okay?
Be very. very still.
Shouldn't the balloons
be closer to my body?
Not if you want to live.
Natasha's balloons are no match
for boris's knives of death!
Boris.
moya lyubov.
spare the life of your lyubov.
Definitely.
Are they sure they know
what they're doing?
You really are as good as you said.
You should try a blindfold.
Yeah. says the half blind woman.
Is it me. or does she seem
a little too into this?
There is. of course. a sexual
component to an act of this sort.
- the knife representing...
- we get it.
Dr. Brennan is showing
remarkable trust and willingness.
Be careful!
She's only got one eye left!
Well. how about that?!
Let's hear it for them. folks.
Boris the brave
and the knee-knockingly lovely natasha!
Come on. boris.
Let them hear it. folks!
They loved us.
You were great.
Superb hand-eye coordination there.
buckie.
I could have killed you.
Therein lies the excitement
for the spectators.
... super strong. mighty magnum!
- Oh. my god.
- What?
Magnum. look!
He definitely has the upper
body strength to swing
the foam barbell hard enough
to cause those fractures.
Check out those arms of steel!
Hey there. big guy.
you got a minute?
For what?
I want to ask you a question
about my friends. Julie and Jenny.
No. this is getting old.
I told you. they were here.
they left. that's all I know.
Check with some
other circuses maybe.
They're dead but you knew that.
didn't you?
Dead?
What are you talking about?
Their heads were smashed together.
Weren't they?
Geez!
- That guy is strong.
- He is called the strongman.
- Help me get out of this.
- I'm trying to get out!
Look. I wanna put a bolo on
this guy right away.
Magnum the strongman. real name:
norman von gluck.
Well. of course he's big.
he's a strongman.
He's wearing a tank top
that says "magnum"...
shouldn't be too hard to spot.
Mr. Nigel-murray has found
some additional bone anomalies.
- Can you explain?
- "Anomaly"
from the greek "anomalos."
I'm thinking we could move this
along a bit faster. mr. Nigel-murray.
I found slight
longitudinal fractures
along the distal ends of all four
lower leg bones and
stress fractures on their cuboids.
Fractures to
the lower legs and feet.
Did the guy torture them first?
Rubber hose to the feet?
That wouldn't be consistent
with the injuries.
which are isolated
to those specific areas.
Can you send me the x-rays?
- The x-rays...
- They're on their way.
I was more than capable
of telling her that.
I was afraid you'd start talking
about wilhelm conrad
and the discovery of the x-ray.
November 8th. 1895.
He made an image of
his wife's hand...
I rest my case.
By the way. we all loved your show.
Oh. thank you.
Did you hear the cheering?
It was all for me.
Booth was undeniably good.
However he's not very imaginative
as far as the act goes.
Look. there is a difference
between imagination
and tempting fate.
I am just asking for a little flair.
- Flair?! You want flair then...
- Can I ask about the eye?
No.
I was thinking that I could wear
a hat of fruit
and then you could slice
through each fruit. while...
Bones. it's over.
No more undercover act.
It's over.
We have to go question
the other performers.
Right.
You two want to explain
what happened with magnum?
- He trapped us in the net.
- For no reason?
- We asked him about the twins.
- Asked what?
If he knew anything
about how they died.
- You want us to take care of this?
- Settle.
- Who are you people?
- Fbi special agent seeley booth.
Dr. Temperance brennan of
the jeffersonian institution.
Okay. the van owen twins
were murdered.
Our prime suspect
right now is magnum.
He had the requisite strength.
Magnum never killed anyone.
People. can you please
come back now?
- Tell them to come back.
- None of us are gonna help you.
Don't you care what
happened to the twins?
You aren't one of us.
You don't get it. do you?
How could you?
You're gillies.
No. no. we're not gillies.
our act was good.
Yeah. you're gillies.
Right.
- We have no case.
- We will when we bring magnum in.
We have no definitive forensics tying
him or anyone else to the murder.
You will when you get back
to the lab. you'll find evidence.
The bonius maximus will have
his initials on it or something.
I really was pretty
good on the high wire.
I'm going to try it.
No. up there now?
Wait a second. bones. no!
You'll fall. it's too high!
- There's a net.
- You got no depth perception.
You have a patch on your eye.
You won't be able to see!
But no. it's more
a case of feel. Booth
I could do it with my eyes shut.
You shut your eyes and I will
shut mine'cause I am not watching.
My teacher said I was
one of his best students.
This is crazy.
Look!
No. I told you. I'm not gonna look.
i'm keeping my eyes shut.
This is absolutely...
oh. my god!
Bones. whoo!
Wow. you are fearless!
My feet! I'm not in shape for this.
Look at you. you're doing great!
You think maybe you could
ride a bike on that thing?
And maybe spin a ball on
your nose at the same time?
Ow! My cuboids!
- Your what?
- The cuboids are the bones in my feet.
You all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Oh. my god!
Bones. are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
- I know what happened.
- It's obvious. you lost your balance.
No. to the twins.
They weren't murdered.
The stress fractures
to their fibulas and cuboids.
they were caused by walking
on the high wire.
And the kissing fracture.
their heads snapped together
when they fell into the net.
That's why there
was no other trauma.
A conjoined twin high-wire act?
Henry said that Jenny
wanted to be famous.
Their act would have
been completely unique.
Well. that's a first.
Yeah. covered up an accident by
making it look like a murder.
I didn't kill the them.
I didn't kill them.
I loved them.
I would never hurt them.
We know.
I buried them.
They needed a proper burial.
Don't say anything. magnum.
You asked them not
to go on the high wire.
but that's exactly what
they wanted to do.
It's probably the only thing
Julie and jenny ever agreed on.
When they dropped to the net.
the force of the fall
snapped their heads together.
An accident like that.
their mother definitely would've sued.
The circus would
never have survived.
You know. I'm going to have to arrest
you for interference with a dead body.
We're sorry. Aren't we?
- Sorry.
- We're going to get you a good lawyer.
Just don't bring them into this.
I don't want to see
the circus die because of me.
What you're going to have to explain.
is why you wrapped them in a sheet
because that's something a woman
would do out of respect.
You'll also have to explain how you
forged their handwriting on a note.
I will.
Thanks.
Well. I'll just call up the dallas
field office.
- and have them pick him up.
- Think he'll run again?
No
He won't run.
They're gone.
Yeah.
- We slept through it?
- Yeah.
"Boris and natasha
and their russian knives of death."
I guess we all got it in us. huh?
The desire to run off
and join the circus.
We did it.
Buck and wanda were damn good.
Buck was more dashing than you.
I mean. Buck drove a motorcycle.
- Wanda was funner than you.
- How?
Well. she let me knock off a rubber
nose from her face with a knife.
You would never let me do that.
You're way too rational.
Where do you think they are now?
Over the horizon.
Subtitle: A²S Team
--==All-about-Subs.fr==--